you should have seen me you should have
seen me that huh
yeah all right yeah man see these hands
wait a minute why hasn't the energy from
my fish transferred into his head yet
wait he ducked literally how I put so
much speed and force into this I
couldn't even imagine dodging something
like this on such short notice he had to
have already known exactly what angle
and speed I would be coming from
okay maybe I'm guessing them up I'm
gonna look on his face it looks like it
was just pure reaction I'll just pull
back and catch him with a follow-up
attack
[Music]
okay I literally can't pull my hand back
there Nurse it is crazy I guess the best
I could do is just spread my feet and
regain balance
oh no that's it I've never swung this
hard before my body wasn't prepared and
now I'm gonna follow my back and when I
do he's gonna hit me he's gonna hit me
with the meanest with punish in human
history and I'm gonna die
who
you look stupid get on my face man
I was wrong
this is worse than with punish
my pride